얜 복실이구요
얜 핏쥬
This kitty is Mittens.
This one is Fitzhugh.
고양이 집에 있는 얜
징키스예요
And this little guy
in the cat condo is Jinkies.
고양이를 많이 키우는군요, 조린?
That's a lot of cats, Jo Lynn.
미혼이죠?
Single, are you?
- 제가 받죠
- 그래요
- I'll get it.
- Okay.
챈들러 빙입니다
Chandler Bing.
네가 왜 직접 받냐?
또라이 비서는 어디가구?
How come you're answering your own
phone? Where's your crazy assistant?
당신은 또라이 아니에요
You're not crazy. You're not crazy.
고양이를 그렇게
여러마리 키우게 두지 않겠죠
Otherwise, why would you
have all those cats?
무슨 일이야?
What's up, Joe?
우리가 늘 같이하고
싶어했던 일이 뭐지?
What have we always wanted
to do together?
서로 머리 땋아주고
말타고 해변달리기?
Braid each other's hair
and ride horseback on the beach?
아니!
내일 우리
No. No. No. When you get home
tomorrow night..
닉스팀 경기 보러가자
코트 바로 옆자리야!
you and I are gonna be
at the Wizards-Knicks game, courtside!
코트 옆자리? 죽인다!
- Courtside? Oh, my God!
- Yeah!
마이클 조던이 공 잡다가 무릎으로
내 턱을 갈길지도 몰라!
Maybe Michael Jordan will dive for
the ball and break my jaw with his knee!
신난다!
모니카한테 얘기할게
That is so cool. I'll let Monica know.
결제해주세요
These need your signature.
조린, 아깐 내친구 조이였는데
아무나 다 또라이라고 하는 애예요
Listen, Jo Lynn, that was my friend Joey.
He calls everybody crazy.
- 여보세요?
- 자기야, 나야
- Hello?
- Hey, hon, it's me.
안녕, 자기야
또라이 비서는 잘지내?
Hi. How's the crazy cat lady?
조이가
Joey just called.
내일 저녁 농구경기 표
사놨다고 같이보재
He's got courtside Knicks tickets
for him and me tomorrow night.
내일 저녁은 일주일에
하루쉬는 날인데?
But tomorrow night's the only night
I get off from the restaurant.
자기 농구 보러가면 우리가 함께
보내는거 일주일 더 기다려야해
If you go, we won't have
a night together for a week.
코트 옆자리야!
치어리더들이 코앞에서..
But honey, it's courtside!
The cheerleaders will be right in..
이렇게 얘기하면
더 안보내주겠지?
That's not the way to convince you.
나 "가지마! 나랑 같이 있어!"
I don't wanna be one
of those wives that says:
이런 말하는 마누라 되기 싫어
"You can't go to the game.
You have to spend time with me."
그러니까 자기가 알아서
깨달았으면 좋겠어
So if you could just realize it
on your own..
자기 말이 맞아
나도 자기 보고싶어
I know. You're right.
I wanna see you too.
그나저나 조이한텐 뭐라고 하지?
굉장히 기대하고 있던데..
I gotta figure out a way to tell Joey.
He's looking forward to it.
마누라 못본지
오래 됐다고 해
Tell him you haven't seen
your wife in a long time.
주말 부부가 얼마나
힘든지 얘기하라구
Tell him that having a long-distance
relationship is really difficult.
함께 있을 시간이 너무 적어서
굉장히 소중하다고 말야
Tell him that what little time
we have together is precious.
내가 알아서 생각해볼게
I'll think of something.
프렌즈 시즌 9
'레이첼의 전화번호'
와!
너 정말..
You look..
그러니까..
그 드레스..
I mean, it's just..
That dress..
그 문장 끝은 좋은거지?
Well, I hope the ends
of these sentences are good.
그럼, 물론이지
이런 모습 오랫만에 보네
They're good. It's just been a while
since I've seen you like this.
아주 말쑥해!
You clean up good.
고마워
Really? Well, thank you.
그만! 그렇게 쳐다보지마
Okay, stop looking at me like that.
지난번에 그렇게 쳐다봤다가
이렇게 됐잖아
- Last time that happened, that happened.
- Right, right.
맞아
엠마 두고 첫 외출
하려니까 어때, 신나?
So are you excited about
your first night away from Emma?
응! 피비랑 정말 신나게 놀거야!
Yeah, yeah. Phoebe and l
are gonna have so much fun.
- 외출하는 동안 엠마 봐줘서 고마워
- 아냐
- Thank you for watching the baby.
- It's fine.
그리고 집으로
마이크 초대했어
Actually, I invited Mike over.
- 피비 남자친구?
- 그래
- Phoebe's Mike?
- Yeah.
- 두사람 친한줄 몰랐네
- 안친해
- I didn't know you hung out.
- We don't..
이번 기회에
친해져 보지, 뭐
but I'd like to get to know him.
식사도 하고, 술도 한잔하고
대화도 하면서 말이지
Maybe have a little dinner,
drinks, conversation.
어머, 오붓해라!
로스와 마이크의 첫번째 데이트네!
That's so cute.
Ross and Mike's first date.
데이트는 무슨..
It's not a date.
하지만, 뭔일이 진행되면
방해하지마
But if it turns out to be
something more..
문 손잡이에다
넥타이 걸어 놓을게
I'll leave a tie on the door.
어색하지 않을까?
만나서 무슨 얘기하려구?
Will that be awkward?
What are you gonna talk about?
몰라, 어쨌든 공통점이 많잖아
I don't know. But you know, we have
a lot in common, you know?
피아노 친다며?
나도 대학때 키보드 쳤잖아
He plays piano.
I played keyboards in college.
이혼경력도 있다면서?
나도 그 방면엔 경험이 있고
He's been divorced.
I have some experience in that area.
- 들어오세요
- 안녕?
- Yeah?
- Hi!
아가씨들의 화끈한 외출이군!
Girl's night out indeed.
엠마가 계속 자겠지만
So I think Emma is probably
down for the night..
- 혹시 무슨일 생기면..
- 괜찮아
- but if you need anything..
- We'll be fine.
- 걱정말고 다녀와
- 자기도 재미있게 놀아
- You go have fun.
- Okay, you too.
그리고 잘해봐
- Thanks.
- And I hope you score.
- 안녕
- 다녀와요
- Okay. Bye.
- Bye.
잘왔어요
So, welcome.
- 맥주좀 가져왔어요
- 집엔 모유가 좀 있어요
- I got beer.
- I got bottled breast milk.
- 맥주부터 마실까요?
- 좋아요
- Why don't we start with the beer.
- Okay.
- 피아노 친다면서요?
- 네
- So Phoebe tells me you play piano.
- Yeah.
나도 대학때 키보드를 쳤어요
You know, I used to play keyboards
in college.
지금 여기 있어요?
Do you have one here?
아뇨
No.
그렇군요
Okay.
난 이혼했어요
You know, I'm divorced.
피비 말이 마이크도
이혼했다면서요?
Phoebe.. Phoebe says you're..
You've been divorced?
네
Yeah, yeah.
미안하지만 그 얘긴
별로 하고 싶지 않군요
Yeah, I'm sorry. I don't really like
to talk about it.
그래요
다른 얘기하죠, 뭐
That's okay. We'll talk about
something else.
- 아파트가 멋지네요
- 고마워요
- This is a nice apartment.
- Thanks.
오리지널 건축장식이에요
The moldings are all original.
제가 사는 아파트는 건축장식이
오리지널인지 모르겠어요
I don't know if the moldings
are original in my apartment.
- 고생물학자라구요?
- 네
- So you're a paleontologist, right?
- Yeah.
- 사촌도 고생물학자예요
- 그래요?
My cousin's a paleontologist.
그 사촌 만나면 할 얘기가
많을것 같네요
Well, he and I would probably have
a lot to talk about.
- 어서와
- 오, 이게 누구야?
- Welcome home.
- Well, look at you.
어때?
Yeah. What do you think?
멋있어, 실은..
Well, it looks great. It's just..
나도 속에 같은거 입었어
I'm wearing the same thing
underneath, so..
무슨 뜻인지 알지?
You see what I mean?
아야!
야, 문 왜 잠궜어?
Hey! How come your door's locked?
- 잠깐만!
- 안돼!
- Just a second!
- No, no, no!
- 나 여기 있는거 조이가 알면 안돼!
- 왜?
- Joey can't know I'm here.
- Why not?
닉스 경기 못간다는 말을
차마 못하겠더라구
I didn't want to say
I couldn't go to the game..
그래서 털사에 계속 있어야
한다고 했어
- so I told him I had to stay in Tulsa.
- So you lied to him?
거짓말했단 말야?
골치 아픈 대화하느니
거짓말이 훨씬 낫잖아!
It's always better to lie than to have
the complicated discussion.
당신한테는 안그러지
Except with you.
문열어! 뭐해?
Hey, open the door! What's going on?
- 뭐하는 거야?
- 안녕
- What are you..?
- Hi.
옷차림이 왜그래?
Why are you dressed like that?
왜냐하면..
며칠 있으면 챈들러 오잖아
Because Chandler's gonna be home
in a couple of days..
그래서.. 유혹하는 기술좀
연습하고 있었어
so I thought I would just, you know,
practice the art of seduction.
남자 목소리가 들린것 같은데?
I thought I heard a man's voice before.
내가 챈들러 역할까지
하면서 연습했거든
No, I was just doing Chandler's side
of the conversation.
"안녕, 나 어때?"
You know, like, "Hi, how do I look?"
"섹시한걸!
후끈 달아오르는구만!"
"Really sexy. Could I be any more
turned on?" You know?
그런데
Okay. Wait a minute.
와인 잔이
왜 두개 나와있지?
Why are there two glasses
of wine out?
하나는 네꺼야!
Because one of them is for you!
건배! 잘가!
Cheers! Okay, bye-bye.
우습지? 나도 혼자 유혹하는
기술 연습하거든
You know, it's funny. I've been
practicing the art of seduction myself.
- 연습 좀더 해
- 알았어
- You might wanna keep practicing.
- Yeah.
- 조이야!
- 뭐?
- It's Joey.
- What?
- 그래, 조이
- 야, 빨리 집에 와!
- Hey, Joe.
- Dude, come home!
- 뭐? 왜?
- 잔말 말고 빨리와!
- What? Why?
- Come home!
안돼! 무슨 일인데?
Look, I can't. What's going on?
뭐라고 해야하나..
모니카가 바람피는것 같아!
I don't know how to tell you this,
but I think Monica's cheating on you!
그러게 너보다 더 매력적인 사람과
결혼하는거 아니랬지!
I told you, you shouldn't have married
someone hotter than you!
네가 집에와서 처리할수 없으면
내가 할게
If you can't deal with this,
then I'm gonna.
- 안돼!
- 방금 그놈 목소리가 났어!
- No!
- I just heard him!
지금도 들려?
Can you hear him now?
아니
들어가봐야겠어!
No. All right, I'm going in.
- 안돼! 기다려!
- 또 들렸어!
- No, wait!
- I heard him again!
그냥 거기있어!
내가 집으로 갈게
All right, just stay there.
I'm coming home.
빨리와
I'll see you when you get here.
난 그놈 도망 못가게
복도에서 지키고 있을게
I'll wait out in the hall
in case he comes out.
- 꼭 그래야만 할까?
- 당연하지, 네가 나였대도 그랬을걸
- Is that really necessary?
- Absolutely. You'd do it for me.
물론 그런일은 없겠지
난 마누라를 만족시킬줄 아니까
Not that you ever have to, because
I know how to keep my women satisfied.
- 그래, 고마워
- 알았어, 있다봐
- Yeah, listen, thanks a lot.
- Okay, bye.
내가 바람피는줄 알잖아?
He thinks I'm a slut.
소방관 옷차림은 아니잖아
Oh, right, and you're
supposed to be a fireman?
피자 올때 되지 않았어요?
Shouldn't the pizza be here by now?
30분안에 온다더니
지금 몇분 됐어요?
I mean, they said 30 minutes or less.
Well, how long has it been?
11분
Eleven minutes.
12분 됐네요
And now 12.
- 우리 TV 볼까요?
- 내가 그 생각 못했을것 같아요!
- So you wanna watch TV?
- You think I haven't thought of that?
내말은, 그러고 싶지만
케이블이 끊겨서요
I mean, I would like to
but the cable's out.
별일 아니라고 생각했는데
그렇지만은 않네요
Didn't seem like such a big deal
until tonight.
- 맥주 좋아해요?
- 그럼요, 좋아해요
- So you like the beer?
- I do. I do.
그중에서 라거를 좋아하죠
Although, it's actually a lager.
그냥 맥주랑 라거랑
뭐가 다르죠?
What's the difference
between beer and lager?
몰라요
I don't know.
한번 찾아볼까요?
We could look it up.
그거 진짜 신나겠는데요
Things are about to get wild.
전엔 우리끼리 이렇게
잘 놀았는데
Oh, God, remember the girls' nights
we used to have..
모여 앉아 너와 로스에 대해
얘기하고 말야
sitting around talking
about you and Ross?
오! 까마득한 옛날 같다
Oh, God! It seems like forever ago.
그래
I know.
로스와는 어떻게 돼가?
So, what's going on
with you and Ross?
모르겠어
별일 없은지 오래됐지
Well, I don't know. I mean,
for a long time, nothing.
그런데 아까 너 오기 직전에
But you know, actually,
right before you picked me up..
사실 일이좀 있었어
Ross and I had a little thing.
어머! 재밌다!
무슨일이 있었는데?
Oh, my God! I love things!
What happened?
먼저 로스가 내 모습이
근사하다고 하더라
Well, first he told me
he liked how I looked.
그리고 잠깐동안 서로..
And then we had a little..
눈을 맞췄지
eye contact.
- 눈을 맞춰?
- 그래
Eye contact?
눈에 보호장치는 했겠지?
I hope you were using protection.
저기 바에 앉아 계신
신사 분들이 내시는 겁니다
Excuse me, these are from
the two gentlemen at the end of the bar.
근데, 저는 한잔 더 못마셔요
아기 모유를 생각해서요
Oh, actually, I can't have another one
on account of my breast milk.
그렇군요
Okay.
레이첼, 좀더 신선한 말로
거절할수 없을까?
Hey, Rach, maybe there's a less
disgusting way to decline a drink.
- 우리도 뭘 보내야 하나?
- 그래! 감자 으깬거 어때?
Should we send them something back?
Let's send them mashed potatoes!
안돼! 그럼
No, wait! Don't do that!
이쪽으로 와도 좋다는
허락으로 생각할거야
That'll make them think
they can come over.
그러면 안돼?
So, what if they do?
우리 남자 만나면 안되잖아, 넌 애인이
있고 난.. 엠마와 로스가 있잖아
We're not here to meet guys. You have
a boyfriend. I have a baby and a Ross.
일 만들것도 아니고
그냥 노는건데, 뭐
Yeah, but nothing has to happen.
We're just having fun.
눈 맞추는것 같은
심각한 일은 안생길 거야
You know, not everything has to go
as far as eye contact.
빨리 조이한테
털사에 있는거 아니라고 불어!
Chandler, you have to tell Joey
you're not in Tulsa.
나한테 속았다고 생각하기 보다
Isn't it better for him
to think you're cheating on me..
당신이 바람핀다고 생각하는게
더 낫지 않을까?
than for him to think
I'm cheating on him?
말 안해도 알아!
I heard it.
조이가 나 바람핀다고
생각하는거 싫단 말야!
I don't want him to think
I'm having an affair.
그럼 이렇게 하자
내가 비상계단으로 내려가서..
All right, I've got a plan.
I'll go down the fire escape..
무슨일만 생기면
비상계단으로 도망간대지
Because all good plans start with,
"I'll go down the fire escape."
끝까지 들어봐!
Hear me out, woman!
비상계단으로 내려가서
밖에서 잠깐 기다릴게
I'll go down the fire escape and wait.
그리고 정문으로 들어오는거야
털사에서 막 온것처럼
Then it'll be like I just got back
from Tulsa.
조이랑 같이 여기 들어와서
아무도 없다는걸 확인하면 되지
Joey and I will come in
and see that there's no guy in here.
조이가 눈치채면 어떡하구?
Aren't you afraid that Joey's
gonna figure all this out?
말 안해도 알아!
I heard it.
- 조금 있다가 나갈래
- 무서운 비둘기 땜에?
- I'm gonna wait.
- The scary pigeon's back?
너무 커!
It's huge.
정말 거기 살아요?
우리 할머니도 거기 사세요!
I can't believe you live in that building.
My grandmother lives in that building!
이름은 아이다고
사적인 공간에 대한 개념이 없죠
Ida Greene? No sense
of personal space..
닭 냄새 비슷하게 나고
감자처럼 생기신..
kind of smells like chicken,
looks like a potato.
- "감자 할머니"가 그쪽 할머니세요?
- 맞아요!
- "Spuds" is your grandmother?
- That's my bubbe!
파티에 갈건데
So we're on our way
to a couple of parties.
분위기 괜찮으면 부를테니
연락처 줄래요?
Maybe we could get your numbers
and call if we find something fun?
미안하지만 우린 두분한테
그런걸 기대하진 않았어요
Yeah. I'm sorry, we weren't really
looking for anything to happen..
난 애인이 있어요
with you guys. I have a boyfriend.
- 알겠습니다
- 괜찮아요
- All right.
- It's no big deal.
궁금해서 그런데
어느분이 내 짝이었어요?
Just out of curiosity,
which one of you was for me?
- 아마도 저였을 거예요
- 멋지시네요
- That would've been me.
- Nice.
다른 상황이었다면
우리 꽤나 재미봤을 텐데
Different situation, cowboy,
and you would've had yourself a handful.
저분은 애인이 있고
그쪽은 어떻죠?
So she has a boyfriend.
What is your situation?
좀 복잡해요
애인이 있는건 아니지만..
Well, it's complicated.
I don't actually have a boyfriend, but..
그럼 연락처 줄래요?
Then can I have your number?
아뇨, 미안해요
I'm sorry, no.
알았어요
Okay.
줄게요!
Oh, sure!
어머! 네 진짜 전화번호잖아!
Oh, my God, you're giving
your real number!
고마워요
이따가 전화할게요
Okay, thanks. I'll give you
a call later tonight.
- 그래요
- 안녕
- Great.
- Bye.
안녕
Bye.
근사하다!
So that's great.
너, 빌, 로스, 엠마!
모두 함께 아주 행복할 거야!
You, Bill, Ross and Emma are
gonna be so happy together.
너 제정신이야?
What were you thinking?
잘생긴데다 날 좋아하잖아!
충동적이었어!
I don't know. He was cute,
and he liked me. It was an impulse.
이 신발 샀을 때처럼
날 예뻐하길래 충동구매를 했지
Like when I bought these shoes.
They were cute and they liked me too.
그럼 로스는?
그 눈맞춤은 어쩌구?
But what about Ross?
What about your moment?
그래, 순간이 있었지
눈맞춤의 순간
We had a moment.
We looked at each other.
이대로 10년을 같이 살면
손을 잡을수도 있겠지
Maybe if we live together
for another 10 years, we may hold hands!
좋았다며
But you were really excited about it.
- 로스한테 얘기할거야?
- 아니!
- Don't you wanna talk to him?
- No.
뭐라고 할지 뻔한걸
No, because I know exactly
how the conversation's gonna go.
"로스, 우리 아까 분위기
좀 묘했지?"
"Hey, Ross, you know, I think
we had a moment before."
"그래, 나도 느꼈어"
"Yeah. Me too."
"하지만 그걸로 뭘
어떻게 하고 싶진 않아"
"Well, but I'm not sure I really want
to do anything about it."
"나도 마찬가지야"
"Yeah. Me neither."
"우리 계속 함께 살면서"
"Should we just live together..
"서로의 감정은 털어놓지 말자"
and not tell each other
how we're feeling?"
"나도 그게 좋겠어"
"Yeah, that works for me."
그래, 무슨 뜻인지 알겠다
Yeah, I see what you mean.
그리고 로스 흉내 아주 잘했어!
By the way, nice Ross imitation.
하지만 레이첼 흉내는
콧소리가 좀 부족했어
Your Rachel wasn't whiny enough.
- 뭐라구?!
- 훨씬 낫다
- Well.. Hey!
- Better.
아무튼 로스와 어떻게 되길
기다리는거 그만하고 싶어
The point is maybe I should just stop
waiting around for moments with Ross.
그냥 내 갈길 가야지
You know? I should just
move on with my life.
정말?
그럼 로스와 정리하려구?
So really, you're moving on from Ross?
모르겠어
당장 결정해야하나?
I don't know.
Do I have to decide right now?
방금 결정했잖아
그 남자 전화 로스가 받으면
You kind of just did.
That guy is gonna call you tonight.
네 뜻은 확실히 전달되는 거지
Ross will pick up the phone,
and that's a pretty clear message.
어머, 정말!
Oh, my God, Ross!
로스가 전화를 받겠구나!
Ross is gonna pick up the phone.
전화번호 돌려달래야겠다!
어떡해! 가버렸어!
I have to get my number back.
Oh, my God, he's gone!
"전화번호 돌려 달래야겠다!
어떡해! 가버렸어!" 똑같지?
"Oh, I have to get my number back!
Oh, my God! He's gone!" Dead on.
- 그만 가볼게요
- 이렇게 빨리요?
- You know, I'm gonna take off.
- So soon?
그래요
- Yeah.
- Okay.
맥주 잘 마셨어요
Well, thanks.. Thanks for the beer.
- 라거 말이죠?
- 그래요, 유익한 시간이었어요
- You mean lager?
- Yeah. Good times.
- 그럼
- 그래요
- Okay.
- All right.
- 여보세요?
- 마이크? 나예요
- Hello?
- Hey, Mike, it's me.
로스옆에 있어요?
Listen, is.. Is Ross near you?
방금 나왔는데요
No, I just left.
작별 인사할때가 오늘 저녁의
대화중 하이라이트였어요
And that, right there, is the most interesting
conversation I've had all night.
정말요? 어쩌나
Really? Okay.
다시 들어가요
Well, you have to go back in.
다시 들어가라구요?
시간이 멈춰버린 그곳으로요?
What? Go back? To the land
where time stands still?
정말 미안해요
I'm so sorry, honey, but..
레이첼이 남자한테
전화번호를 줬는데
Okay, Rachel gave this guy
her number..
로스가 전화 받으면 안돼요!
and she doesn't want Ross
to answer the phone.
마이크가 대신 받아줘요!
So you have to intercept all his calls.
어떻게 그래요!
I can't do that!
- 그렇게 못한대
- 이리줘봐!
- He says he can't do that.
- Give me the phone.
안녕, 마이크?
무리한 부탁인거 알지만
Hi, Mike. Hi, listen, I know that this
is a lot to ask, but you know what?
그렇게만 해주면.. 피비가
원하는거 다 해줄 거예요
If you do this, Phoebe will do
anything you want.
- 화끈하게, 무슨 말인지 알죠?
- 됐어, 이리줘
- Seriously, I'm talking dirty stuff.
- All right. Thank you. Hello?
레이첼 대신 사과할게요, 하지만
"화끈하게"란 말은 틀린 말이 아녜요
Hi, I'm sorry about her. But actually,
she wasn't wrong about the dirty stuff.
알았어요, 할게요
All right, I'll do it.
그런데 얼마나
더 화끈할 건데요?
But really, how much dirtier
can it get?
오, 마이크
Oh, Mike.
끊어요
Bye.
안녕, 로스?
Hey, buddy.
마이크!
Hi.
- 다시 들어가도 돼요?
- 왜요?
- Can I come back in?
- Why?
생각해보니까 우리 할 이야기가
아직 많더라구요
Well, I was just thinking about
how much more we have to talk about.
아까 갔잖아요
But you left.
빨리왔네!
That didn't take long.
털사에서
비행기로 세시간이라며?
I thought you said Tulsa was,
like, a three-hour flight?
시차를 생각해야지
Well, you're forgetting
about the time difference.
- 준비됐냐? 같이 들어가 줄게
- 고마워
- You ready? I'm gonna go in there with you.
- Thanks.
저안에 모니카랑 한명
이상인걸 대비해서
Just in case there's more
than one dude in there.
- 정말 고맙다
- 알았어
- Again, thanks.
- Yeah.
챈들러! 집에 왔네?
Chandler, you're home!
그래! 남편이 왔도다!
바람피던거 당장 멈춰!
That's right! Your husband's home!
So now the sex can stop!
무슨 소린줄 알잖아
You know what I mean.
무슨 소리야?
What are you saying?
조이가 그러는데
외간 남자랑 있다며!
Joey said you're here
with another man!
여기 아무도 없어!
어떻게 날 의심할수가 있어?
There's no man in here!
How dare you accuse me of that!
그럼 나랑 챈들러가
집안 둘러봐도 괜찮지?
All right. Then maybe you won't mind
if me and my friend take a look around.
우릴 보지도 못하는데
왜 때려?
He can't even see us!
- 흥분되더라고
- 나두
- I kind of liked it.
- Me too.
쟤 뭐하는 거야?
What's he doing?
침대 속에 베개를
사람처럼 보이게 넣어뒀어
I arranged some pillows on the bed
to look like a guy.
침실엔 아무도 없어
베개는 새로 사야겠다
Bedroom's clear. Although you might
need some new pillows.
난 손님방 가볼게
All right, well, I'll check
the guest room.
왜 남자향수 냄새가 나지?
Why do I smell men's cologne?
너한테서 나는데?
I think that's you.
맞다! 아까 잡지에 붙은 샘플
몸에 막 문질렀어
Oh, yeah. I rubbed a magazine
on myself earlier.
아무도 없는데?
There's nobody here, Joe.
그러네
I guess not.
어떻게 내가 바람핀다고
의심할 수가 있어? 나한테 사과해!
I can't believe you thought I was cheating.
You owe me an apology.
- 그래, 정말 미안해, 실수잖아
- 그럴수도 있지
- You're right. I'm so sorry.
- It's an honest mistake.
괜찮아, 잘가!
It could happen to anybody. See you.
어, 잠깐만!
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
방금 털사에서 왔다며 어떻게
가방이 너보다 먼저 와있냐?
If you just got back from Tulsa,
how did your suitcase beat you here?
난 비상계단까지 내려갔는데
가방 하나 숨기는게 그렇게 어려워?
I climbed down the fire escape,
and you can't put that in the closet?
그러니까 발효과정만 빼면
So, with the exception
of the fermentation process..
맥주와 에일은
기본적으로 같은 거예요
beer and ale are
basically the same thing.
정말 재미있죠?
Fascinating, isn't it?
"재미있다"도 사전에서
찾아보지 그래요?
Maybe you should look up "fascinating."
내가 받을게요!
I'll get it!
로스 집입니다
전 마이크구요
Hello? Ross' place. Mike speaking.
전화 받아요
It's for you.
조금전에
도대체 왜그런 거예요?
I don't understand
what just happened here.
어떻게 된거야?
What's going on?
미안해
I'm sorry.
저녁에 모니카랑 보내려고
털사에 있다고 거짓말 한거야
I told you I was in Tulsa because I
wanted to spend the night with Monica..
네가 이해 못할것 같아서
and I didn't know..
I didn't think you'd understand.
내가 부부가 함께 있고 싶은것도
이해 못하는 멍청이냐?
You think I'm too dumb to understand
a husband needs to be with his wife?
네눈엔 내가 깡통 같아?
You think I'm, like..
- 조이?
- 왜!
- Joey?
- Yeah.
정말 유구무언이다
널 속이다니 말야
I don't know what to say.
We shouldn't have lied to you.
정말 미안해
어떻게 하면 기분이 풀어지겠냐?
I feel so bad. Is there anything
I can do to make it up to you?
나랑 농구경기 보러가!
못간다고 할거 뻔하지만
You could go to the game with me.
Even though you said you couldn't.
그래도 넌 날 속였고 머리에
혹까지 나게 만들었잖아
But then you lied to me and tricked me
and gave me a bump on the head.
미안하지만, 그것만은 안돼
모니카랑 보내기로 약속했거든
I'm sorry, that's the one thing I can't do.
I promised I'd be with Monica.
알았어
All right.
- 갔다와
- 뭐?
- You can go.
- What?
경기 보러가
괜찮아, 다녀와
You should go to the game.
It's okay. I want you to.
- 정말? 괜찮겠어?
- 그렇다니까
- Really? You gonna be okay?
- Yeah, I'll be fine.
그동안 난 집에서 유혹하는
기술이나 연습하지, 뭐
You know, maybe I'll stay here
and practice the art of seduction.
- 운동복 입고 청소할거지?
- 정말 신날거야!
- You're gonna put sweats on and clean.
- It's gonna be so hot!
다녀와
- Bye.
가자
Thanks.
표 받아
Here's your ticket.
고마워
그리고..
Thanks. Hey, listen..
다시는 너 속이지 않을게
I'm never gonna lie
to you again, okay?
그리고 너 멍청하다고
생각하는 사람 아무도 없어
And I want you to know
that nobody thinks you're stupid.
고마워
Thanks, man.
- 어디가?
- 경기 내일 저녁이잖아
- Where you going?
- Game's tomorrow night, Joe.
로스 어머님이랑 통화해보니깐
참 좋으신 분인것 같아요
I'm glad I got to talk to your mom.
She sounds nice.
맞아요
다정다감한 분이세요
Yeah, she's a peach.
- 안녕
- 어서와
Oh, God!
얼마나 반가운지 모를 거예요!
So glad you're back!
뭐하고 놀았어?
So, what did you guys do?
맥주 마시고
You know, we just drank some beer.
마이크가 비상식적인 행동으로
날 놀랬켰지
Mike played with the boundaries
of normal social conduct.
네, 사실이에요
It's true, I did.
- 그럼 잘있어
- 잘가
- Well, goodbye.
- Okay.
- 재미있었어!
- 그래, 재미있었어
- Bye. That was fun, Phoebe.
- I know. It was fun.
잘가요
See you, guys.
문 잠궈!
빨리 문 잠궈!
Lock the door!
Lock the door, seriously.
참, 피비한테 술값 안줬다
Shoot, I forgot to pay Phoebe
for the drinks.
잠깐만요! 미안해요
그남자 전화 왔어요?
Wait, wait. Wait, sorry.
Did he call? Did that guy call?
로스 어머니만 하셨어요
No, just his mom.
8시 30분 경에요?
Around 8:30?
- 네
- 9시에 또 하셨죠?
- Yeah.
- Then again at 9:00?
네
Yeah.
여보세요?
Hello?
잠깐 나갔는데요
메시지 전해줄까요?
No, she's not here right now.
Can I take a message?
술집에서 만난 빌?
Bill from the bar?
알겠습니다
전화번호 전해줄게요
Okay, Bill from the bar,
I'll make sure she gets your number.
그래..
어땠어?
So.. So how was it?
두사람 재미있었어?
Did you guys..?
You guys have a good time?
아주 재미있었어!
밖에 나가니까 너무 좋더라
We had so much fun.
It felt so good to be out.
레이첼?
Rach?
왜?
Yeah?
아냐
Never mind.
- 안녕
- 어서와요
- Hey, you guys.
- Hey!
잠깐 화장실 다녀올게요
I'll be right back.
I gotta go to the bathroom.
흑맥주!
그것도 맥주의 일종이죠
Stout. That's a kind of beer.